<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bitcoin on Finance with Raja</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1314/tags/bitcoin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bitcoin on Finance with Raja</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2025 Finance with Raja. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1314/tags/bitcoin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Cryptocurrency Guide for Beginners 2025: Everything You Need to Know to Get Started</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/posts/cryptocurrency-guide-beginners-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/posts/cryptocurrency-guide-beginners-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cryptocurrency might seem intimidating if you&amp;rsquo;re just getting started, but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to be. This comprehensive guide will teach you everything you need to know about cryptocurrency in 2025 - from what it is and how it works, to buying your first Bitcoin safely and avoiding common mistakes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By the end of this guide, you&amp;rsquo;ll understand the fundamentals of cryptocurrency and feel confident taking your first steps into the digital currency world.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Government Shutdown Impact on Finance &amp; Crypto Markets 2025: What Investors Need to Know</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1314/posts/us-government-shutdown-finance-crypto-impact-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1314/posts/us-government-shutdown-finance-crypto-impact-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The US government shutdown has created unprecedented uncertainty across financial markets and the cryptocurrency sector. With key regulatory agencies operating at minimal capacity and economic data releases suspended, investors face a challenging environment that demands strategic adaptation and careful risk management.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As federal agencies like the SEC, CFTC, and Treasury Department operate with skeleton crews, the implications ripple through every corner of the financial ecosystem—from traditional stock markets to the rapidly evolving crypto landscape. Understanding these impacts is crucial for protecting your portfolio and identifying opportunities during this period of political dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
